[
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da divisão: 15/3?",
        "choice1": "7",
        "choice2": "6",
        "choice3": "5",
        "choice4": "4",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da divisão: 16/4?",
        "choice1": "8",
        "choice2": "4",
        "choice3": "6",
        "choice4": "3",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da divisão: 28/7?",
        "choice1": "7",
        "choice2": "4",
        "choice3": "3",
        "choice4": "5",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto é 54/9?",
        "choice1": "5",
        "choice2": "7",
        "choice3": "8",
        "choice4": "6",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto é 84/3?",
        "choice1": "24",
        "choice2": "26",
        "choice3": "27",
        "choice4": "38",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto é 65/5?",
        "choice1": "11",
        "choice2": "12",
        "choice3": "13",
        "choice4": "14",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto vale 56/7?",
        "choice1": "6",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "9",
        "choice4": "7",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto vale 63/3?",
        "choice1": "21",
        "choice2": "23",
        "choice3": "25",
        "choice4": "27",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto vale 18/9?",
        "choice1": "9",
        "choice2": "3",
        "choice3": "2",
        "choice4": "10",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da divisão: 72/3/2?",
        "choice1": "24",
        "choice2": "12",
        "choice3": "48",
        "choice4": "16",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 2
    }
]